{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","address":"4300 Cadieux  Rd","zipcode":"48224","owner":"Cadieux Cafe, Inc.","licenseNumber":"034013","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/24/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000078CF7B754BBB54C030C57CE365334540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43245","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","inspectionDate":"2018-08-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43245","inspectionDate":"8/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"43245","inspectionDate":"8/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43245","inspectionDate":"8/23/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"41472","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","inspectionDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41472","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the FILTERS","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"41472","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Chipped","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"41472","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"41472","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"41472","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s)","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the floor LID","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"41472","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"5-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables used with materials containing FOOD residue and used outside the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be designed and constructed to have tight-fitting lids, doors, or covers.\r\n(B) Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE and recyclables such as an on-site compactor shall be installed so that accumulation of debris and insect and rodent attraction and harborage are minimized and effective cleaning is facilitated around and, if the unit is not installed flush with the base pad, under the unit.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"dumpster","problemDescription":"With doors,lids or covers","subProblem":"Left open","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"At the Dumpster(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep closed."}]},{"inspectionid":"39541","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","inspectionDate":"2017-08-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39541","inspectionDate":"8/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"39541","inspectionDate":"8/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser Holster(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"39541","inspectionDate":"8/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39541","inspectionDate":"8/7/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37720","establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","inspectionDate":"2017-01-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"318"}}